[Music]
yeehaw
oh
I'm not here to get [ __ ] in the
yesterday sheriff I'm just here to grab
in fact their number one Sonic
a drink
i need to make sure I'm hydrated for
when I get [ __ ] in the ass tonight
by like 6 guys
just get me a bottle of water old man
I’ve been on a diet lately to keep my
boobs and butt cheeks in peak condition
i want to look good in my next wanted
poster
eight by the way it seems there are
quite a few of new faces in this alone
today
would you mind filling me in on who they
are
yeah it rocks like a sand storm last
night broke in a lot of new travellers
in cars
you definitely don't want to start a
game with him he's taking a verity from
you
ever since a table
wanted
his sister Sonia and his brother maddox
have a band they're already in the top
in fact their number one Sonic
Underground wanted
for fun also
this guy hey bro me and Sonia are
finished setting up the instruments
what do you say we do it to it and give
the saloon the best damn show they'll
ever experience
[Music]
was it it rocks liquidator about to
start drinking
you're ready for a
[Music]
feeling sauvage in between these ears
ain't nothing good
gotta get my fix so it's time for me to
go
[Music]
gonna get on down this once for me
all I gotta do is find my keys and by
then I should be headed on down the road
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
[Applause]
what in tarnation I’ve never seen
somebody like him around these hair
parts
does anybody know who he is he can't
believe it
he know is what he always talked it was
so evert levy and this is the sturdy
enriched
cowboy in the west what kind of
mechanical doohickey is he riding
that doesn't look like any old horse to
me that's because it's not ours
and the special one
but I thought carl benz from germany
said he was going to be finished
building the first car in a few years
in the year 1885 was it roxy curses over
cleveland
into it I hear that horseshoe Bartleby
is so rich
that instead of robbing banks he buys
them then fires everybody
who worked there he's the epitome of
evil
although you gotta admit he is kind of
cute
everybody get back
into salon
[Music]
I'm sorry did I say you could look at me
howdy sheriff my body seems to have
filled up with a lot of poop during my
travels
you got a bathroom in this place so i
could take a massive stinky [ __ ]
um
[Music]
[Applause]
now that I'm finished duping you're
going to put all the money you got into
this bag
see
[ __ ] hold on I left the bag by the
toilet
no old man you're going to give me all
the money you've got
if you value your life
howdy sir what business does one as big
as you have with a Hedgehog as small as
me
hey [ __ ] you wanna hear a secret i
didn't actually come here to rob the
place
i have actually been traveling all
around these wild wild west
looking for a true challenge another
cowboy who can defeat me in an
old-fashioned shootout
i have killed over 18 000 cowboys so far
because none are as good as me and well
i couldn't help
but notice your fat ass and I was
thinking [ __ ]
maybe just maybe you could give me the
challenge I have been looking for
are you challenging me to a shootout i
don't know what would happen
if I declined i'll tell you what will
happen if you decline bitch
first i'd kill everybody else in this
room then I would rape your cute little
ass
ugh
[Music]
so tell me bandit Sonic you know what a
western shootout is
can't say I have I would hate to kill
such a sexy man like yourself
before you can show me what you are made
of
would you like for me to explain the
rules first go on
so we can finish this sooner and you can
leave this town and never return
listen carefully because I'm only going
to explain this once
the rules are as simple as the recipe
for my money's sweet apple
pie we start off on opposite sides of
the road
our eyes locked onto each other a
revolver is in our holster on our sides
next to our butt cheeks on the count of
three we draw our weapon and fire
whoever is hit
loses the jewel it's that simple and
i'll tell you now
i don't lose
[Music]
that sounds simple enough so does that
mean we're doing this thing or what
one three
run away fatty the bullets gonna get you
of all my time in the wildest of west
you have been the first one to survive
against me
tell me bandit Sonic how did you do it
oh
i know it was your big [ __ ] ass
that's enough my brother already
challenged you and he lived
this duel is over it's funny how you
defend him
yet you don't even know his deepest
darkest secret
secrets bro what is he talking about
go on tell everyone what you're really
called around here
the fake name you use in the dead of
night when you're out stealing [ __ ]
we're dying to hear the truth bandit
Sonic or should I call you
big buttt bob big buttt bob
bro you're the infamous big buttt bob the
dangerous outlaw that goes out at night
to steal people's things
that's right it's me I am the one known
as big butt bob
i am not only a cowboy but an outlaw of
the shadows wanted all over the west
I'm sorry you had to find out like this
my own bro
now listen here bandit Sonic I'm willing
to give you an offer
you can either stay here in this town
and I kill everyone in it
including you or the other option which
i believe you may much prefer
you come with me and become my personal
bitch and we can ride off into the
sunset together in my fancy new
limousine
no I'm not making you pick one or the
other but I believe we all know which
one you want more
you say that but it doesn't feel like i
get much of a choice here
i don't know maybe it's because you're
currently squeezing my big ass
but I think i'll pick the second option
okay
[Music]
is
there are things that make
you